Contact

1687 N 300 E Pleasant Grove Utah 8019695294 (Mobile) kagensmith27@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kagen-smith (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Payment Industry
Security Awareness
Customer Experience

Kagen Smith

Actor | Full Stack Web Developer Student | Customer Service Pleasant Grove, Utah, United States

Summary

I currently have 6 years of customer support experience. I also have experience in acting on stage and some voice acting though I have yet to be casted in a paid project. I was a scare actor for a local haunted house where I play hockey masked killers, zombies, chainsaw wielding maniacs, etc. I am also a student at a coding bootcamp, here is my GitHub profile, https://github.com/Kagen-Smith

Experience

Shadows of fear

Actor

September 2020 - Present (4 years 1 month)

Pleasant Grove, Utah, United States

I'm a scare actor, I dress up and act as several different characters to scare and entertain guests.

Holiday Oil Co.

Cashier

September 2023 - Present (1 year 1 month)

Utah, United States

SecurityMetrics

Customer Service Representative

August 2022 - June 2023 (11 months)

Orem, Utah, United States

I handled inbound and outbound calls to help people with their PCI compliance.

Atento

Phone/chat agent

November 2021 - July 2022 (9 months)

Lindon, Utah, United States

I've been a phone agent and a chat agent. I accept customers calls and provide them with the best care I can give and make sure I answer any

questions they may have. I also placed orders and replacements on behalf of customers

Purple Turtle

Cashier

February 2020 - October 2021 (1 year 9 months)

Pleasant Grove, Utah, United States

I handled the cash registers at the drive thru and the front desk.

Lamplight Theatre

Cast member

September 2019 - October 2019 (2 months)

Draper, Utah, United States

I was cast in a community theater production of Sweeney Todd: the Demon Barber of Fleet Street where I played Beatle Bamford

Little Caesars Pizza

Team Member

November 2018 - October 2019 (1 year)

Pleasant Grove, Utah, United States

Larry H. Miller Megaplex Theatres

Food court team member

December 2017 - October 2018 (11 months)

Vineyard, Utah, United States

I worked the food court where I handled guests orders and got them their food or drink

Arby's

Cashier

May 2017 - September 2017 (5 months)

American Fork, Utah, United States

I worked the front cash register as well as the drive thru register. I also handled packaging food and making fried items

Education

University of Utah

coding · (June 2024 - November 2024)

Pleasant Grove High School

· (August 2015 - May 2019)